Adam Mosebach

Full Stack Web Developer New York. NY

Professional Summary

I am a developer with a passion for thinking outside the box. I believe there are many solutions to achieving a goal and love finding the best one. I am a fun-loving but focused person who finds fulfillment in completing a task. Efficiency and user experience fuel my logical approach to crafting the ideal program.

Related Experience

Software Engineering Immersive Fellow

General Assembly | New York | 2020-Present

- Learned many front-end and back-end languages and how they are implemented in the real wold
- Worked in teams to create a collaborative atmosphere, making the project better than any one person could have done
- Created four complete projects using the skills we learned in class

Morgan Stanley

Programmer | New York | 2006-2007

- Wrote automated processes for incoming trade records to be ingested and analyzed
- Provided error reporting for both the client and Morgan Stanley
- Provided customer service to large firms when further action was needed on client side
- Built a series of training videos to help incoming colleagues perform and onboard efficiently

Other Work

AJ Karaoke

Founder, Owner, Operator | 2014-Present

- Combined many machines to create a full setup for audio and visual technology
- Used Virtual DJ program to implement songs and project lyrics to screen
- Consistently updated the online catalog using a database and elementary php

Professional Actor

Various Locations | 2007-2019

 Actor (and sometimes assistant stage manager) in various theaters across America, including a national tour and an international tour

Contact

Phone: 516.721.2784

Email: aimose@aol.com

LinkedIn/in/adammosebach

Technical Skills

JAVASCRIPT REACT

HTML GIT

CSS RUBY

EXPRESS RUBY ON RAILS

NODE.JS POSTGRESQL

MONGO DB COMMAND LINE

MONGOOSE RESPONSIVE DESIGN

Education

Certificate of Completion

General Assembly

New York, NY

Bachelor of Fine Arts

- minor in Computer Applications

NYU

New York, NY

Portfolio

AdamMosebach.dev